imts.com 2015-06-10

# Privacy Policy | International Manufacturing Technology Show 2016

#### Effective May 13, 2013

Welcome to the website for the International Manufacturing Technology Show ("IMTS"), which is brought to you by AMT - The Association For Manufacturing Technology ("AMT"). This Privacy Policy describes the types of information collected through the IMTS website, www.imts.com, (the "Site") and the ways in which AMT may use, disclose, and protect that information. Please note that this Privacy Policy does not apply to other sites and services operated by AMT. Please be sure to review this entire Privacy Policy carefully before submitting any information through the Site. If you have any questions about our privacy practices, please refer to the end of this Policy for information on how to contact us.

AMT may update this Privacy Policy to reflect changes in our practices and services. When we post changes to this Policy, we will revise the "effective" date at the top of this page and the new version will be effective from the time it is posted. This Privacy Policy outlines the online data collection, use, and disclosure practices of AMT with respect to personal information collected from you through the Site (a "User").

### Collection of Personal Information

AMT receives and stores any information you enter on our website. This includes information that can identify you ("personal information"), such as your name, postal address, e-mail address, telephone number, and billing information (such as credit card number, cardholder name, and expiration date). We also may request information about the company for which you work and your job function. You can choose not to provide us with any personal information, but some information about you is required in order for you to register as a member, ask a question, or initiate other transactions on our site.

In addition, when you visit the Site, your browser automatically transmits certain information to AMT, such as the location of your computer on the Internet, that could, in connection with other information, be identified as coming from you. Further, as discussed below, AMT may use cookies and other Web technologies on the Site, which may enable AMT to collect additional information.

* * *

### Use of Personal Information

AMT uses personal information collected on the Site for administrative, analytical, and marketing purposes related AMT’s operations, including operation of the Site. For example, we use personal information to determine whether a User is authorized for access to members-only or other restricted-access areas, to fulfill orders for publications, to register Users, to provide customer support, and to identify, develop, market and deliver other products and services to you. In addition, AMT may also use information collected on the Site to communicate with you, to analyze your use of the Site, to improve the content and functioning of the Site, and for other internal business purposes.

* * *

### Disclosure of Personal Information

AMT may disclose your information to third-party service providers, vendors, suppliers, content providers, and consultants of AMT or its affiliates for purposes of AMT’s operations and in order to respond to requests made by you or to aid in the maintenance and operation of the Site. AMT may also disclose your information to prospective and current sponsors and exhibitors at AMT events, including the IMTS, who may contact you about products and services in which we hope you are interested. In addition, AMT may disclose your personal information:

  * (a) In response to a subpoena or similar investigative demand, a court order, or a request for cooperation from a law enforcement agency, state and federal regulatory agency, or other government agency; to establish or exercise our legal rights; to defend against legal claims; or whenever AMT otherwise believes that it is required by law to do so. In such cases, we may raise or waive any legal objection or right available to us.
  * (b) When we believe disclosure is appropriate in connection with efforts to investigate, prevent, or take other action regarding suspected fraud or other wrongdoing; to enforce our Terms of Use; to protect the safety or property interests of AMT and its employees; or to protect the safety of the public.

AMT may use in any manner, and disclose to third parties, aggregated information about Users in a form that does not personally identify you.

* * *

### Tracking and Facilitating Site Usage

AMT may use cookies (small unique identifiers) and other technologies to recognize you and facilitate your access privileges on the Site, as well as to track Site usage. Users whose browsers are configured not to accept cookies may not be able to access all or part of the Site. Some links found on the Site may contain or result in the use of cookies that are set by third parties. AMT does not control and is not responsible for such cookies. AMT also logs technical information, such as the location of your computer on the Internet, for systems administration and troubleshooting purposes.

* * *

### Protection of Personal Information

AMT employs a variety of security measures to help protect your personal information from unauthorized access and disclosure. For example, only employees of AMT and employees of third-party hosting services, vendors, suppliers, content providers, or consultants are permitted access to personal information of Users in the course of operating the Site, and they may do so only for permitted business functions. AMT also encourages its third-party hosting services, vendors, suppliers, content providers, and consultants to abide by this Privacy Policy. Although we take steps to protect your personal information, please note that no Internet transmission is 100% secure or error-free. Therefore, we do not promise, and you should not expect, that your personal information or other communications will always remain private. AMT cannot assume, and expressly disclaims, to the maximal extent permitted by law, any responsibility or liability for any information collected by AMT or any other party or for any use, misuse, disclosure, or improper disclosure of such information.

* * *

### Third-Party Websites

The Site may contain hyperlinks to websites of affiliates, advertisers, or others. Such sites are operated by third parties and are not under the control of AMT. Personal information that you provide to third-party sites is not covered by this Privacy Policy, and AMT does not have any control over third-party sites' collection, use, or disclosure of your personal information. Likewise, disclosures made to third parties unaffiliated with AMT using any feature of the Site are not covered by this Privacy Policy with respect to those third parties' uses or disclosures of your personal information. AMT has no control over persons or entities to whom you may send personal information, and it is your responsibility to protect against unwanted use or disclosure of information provided to third parties using any feature that may be offered by AMT.

* * *

### Access to Personal Information

If you have provided personal information to register as a member or in response to a specific request for personal information from AMT, you may update or correct your personal information by contacting AMT through the means listed at the end of this Privacy Policy.

* * *

### Consent to Collection, Use, and Disclosure of Personal Information

By providing personal information to AMT or otherwise using the Site, you consent to AMT's collection, use, and disclosure of such information in accordance with this Privacy Policy, and to the other statements in the Privacy Policy, as it may be revised. You should check the Site regularly for changes to the Privacy Policy. AMT may, in its sole discretion, use other or additional means to notify you of changes in this Privacy Policy. If we make any material changes to this Privacy Policy, we will notify you by sending an e-mail to the e-mail address that you most recently provided to us, and/or by prominently posting notice of the changes on the Site.

* * *

### IMTS E-mail Privacy Policy

IMTS is committed to your privacy and protecting your information. This statement is to explain how the information you share with us is used.

We only share your information with IMTS official partners and exhibitors with your express advance permission. Visitors can opt out of receiving e-mail from these entities initially through the registration process, and at any time by calling the CDS customer service hotline at [508.743.8535](tel:5087438535).

**Please note:** If you share your information with IMTS partners or exhibitors through other channels, this is considered a separate relationship with that company and is not covered by this privacy policy. Examples of sharing include scanning your badge at a booth, or accepting an invite through the Customer Invitation Program.

* * *

### Site Use on Behalf of Another

If you enter information or otherwise use the Site on behalf of another person or entity, you consent both on your own behalf and on behalf of that other person or entity to AMT's collection, use, and disclosure of such information, whether it is information of yours or information of such other person or entity, in accordance with this Privacy Statement. You also represent and warrant that you have the authority to consent on behalf of such other person or entity.

* * *

### Contact Information

If you have any questions or comments about this Privacy Policy or the collection or use of personal information by AMT, or if you wish to opt out of any e-mail list, you may contact AMT by writing a letter to IMTS Webmaster, 7901 Westpark Drive, McLean, VA 22102, or by sending an e-mail to [webmaster@imts.com](mailto:webmaster@imts.com).
